This gothic structure began its
life as a 14th century castle.
Converted into a hotel in the early 1900s,
it closed 10 years ago
when the owner died.
Now, Kars is using the ancient
building as a shelter from the sun.
He lurks within, waiting.
Alas, JoJo and Lisa Lisa know
nothing of the hotel's layout.
Really would it kill you to sweep a bit
okay I get it scary monsters don't do.
Much house cleaning but that does leave
evidence see this blood trail it seems.
As though Wamuu took a good hum on
thrashing Caesar didn't go down without.
Giving a good account of himself?
We mustn't let Wamuu heal anymore!
Coach Lisa Lisa, it's
time for some action!
What is it?
Uh, it's just...
Well, when I took a hold of this
doorknob, it wasn't pleasant.
It felt like I was grabbing the
hand of something cold and dead.
I'm not the door! Where's that?
Why are you looking around?
I'm not a door, but I am here! What?
That's... that's a...
A vampire!
Careful, Jojo!
Jojo!
If it weren't for your little Yuya there,
I would've peeled your
face right off your head!
Hi, I'm Wyatt Beck and
I'll be slaying you now!
I killed my sweetheart, but
then I busted out of prison.
In no time, Lord Kars took me in
and made me part of his little gang.
He's got my loyalty.
And I'm not going to let
you go in there and disturb
Lord Kars when he's enjoying
a well-deserved rest.
So they've done it. It's begun.
They've started unleashing their
demon hounds on the weak and innocent.
Stop that noise!
You're just another vampire who's
bound for hell and leaving now.
Well then, let me help you plan your trip
so you don't have to wait any longer.
Huh?
Lisa, Lisa.
You're beautiful, magnificent.
Your skin is so soft, heavenly, and clear.
Let me hold you, and then I'll drink
your life right through that skin.
You're really not impressing me. Hmm?
I refuse to waste my time listening to
your weak flirtations and shallow threats.
But if you want to hold me,
go ahead and give it a try.
I guarantee it'll be the
last thing that you do.
Spikes!
He's covered top to bottom!
They're popping out of him like
hundreds of pointed fingers!
They're metallic and racist
sharp, like an Iron Maiden jacket!
I don't appreciate it when stuck-up
females are insulting like that.
They need to be punished.
Wouldn't you agree?
I'll give you a nice squeeze!
I'm going to hug you to death! Oh, no!
He's a lot faster than I thought he was!
Wait, I see.
Her scarf becomes a hormone-filled
weapon with incredibly long reach.
Huh?
Gosh, thanks for the thought.
You can't catch me like that.
Don't make me laugh.
See, I'm free.
Hmm, that's all?
Where do you think you're going?
Come, Jojo, let's go.
Uh, okay.
Lisa Lisa's movements, they're
effortless and flow like silk.
Efficient, she doesn't waste any energy.
Come back, you can't just walk away.
Hey, you!
Wouldn't you agree that a woman who
behaves like that needs to be punished?
Oh, no, you are the one being punished.
You see, you've just run out of time.
Harmon is now running
all through your body.
Huh?
Don't be ridiculous, I'm not. Ah!
Oh, no!
Lisa, Lisa has really got what it takes.
I thought she might be out
of her depth in a fight.
But it's plainly obvious
she's even better than me.
I am so impressed.
I'm lucky to have her training me.
By the way, Jojo.
Have you taken it?
You really shouldn't delay any longer.
You must use the antidote! Huh?
Oh, you mean this?
Yes, of course.
I'm going to drink it
only after I defeat Wamu.
See this ring?
It no longer signifies a
promise between me and Wamu.
It's now a promise I make to Caesar, that
I will go on living and stay in the fight.
Would you please hold it for me
until I actually need it, Lisa-Lisa?
No.
It would be better if it stayed with you.
Who knows what might happen to me?
Huh?
As they ventured further into the depths,
the trail of blood grew ever thinner.
Both Jojo and Lisa Lisa knew well what
meaning could be drawn from that fact.
Wamuu's Hamon wounds were healing.
So you're here.
I've been waiting.
I see your powers have grown greatly.
Bastard!
You're the one who killed Caesar! Now I...
Cool your head, Jojo.
Now look at the floor.
I'm very calm.
Don't worry, I'm in control here.
You mean the footprints, right?
I noticed it too.
There are two sets.
That means Kars is here!
Tell me where I can fight him!
Show your cowardly self now!
Indeed, there are two sets
of footprints. He's here.
But I feel dozens of lungs moving
the air around as well. Huh?
So it's you.
Fascinating.
You are extremely composed and perceptive,
though you are a woman.
I can see how Jojo and
Caesar we're able to learn so
much so quickly and you can feel
even the lightest? respiration.
You rank among the
finest Hormone warriors.
Damn!
Look at that!
There's so many!
I'd guess you're all
vampires, is that right?
No response.
That's creepy too.
Khaas!
Lord Khaas saw fit to give us, his
chosen ones, the gift of eternal life.
We, number a hundred,
on our master's order, we'll tear you both
to shreds, a hundred against two! Jojo!
You fiends!
This really is not good.
It's a hundred of them
against the two of us.
We can't win!
Lord Kars, a moment.
Back in Rome, Jojo and I promised
to fight one another again.
I want revenge for ACDC.
Please allow me the chance to fight him.
No.
Remember that my goal is only
to obtain the Red Stone of Asia.
Don't forget that, Wamuu.
Yes, Lord.
Oh, darn. No fight.
Well, I'm not in the mood anyway.
Of course we both know I would beat you.
But to what end?
All these vampires are here.
What sort of motivation
is that, I ask you?
Win or lose, I would still
come out of it dead, right?
With odds like that, giving up
is the only rational choice.
So I'm throwing in the towel.
Damn.
Had to try.
I thought it was worth a shot.
Even if you were watching all the
time, a Hamonet was a good idea.
Kill them without any further delay.
Your choice.
But if you kill us, you'll
never get the stone.
Hold it.
What are you saying now, woman?
You don't think I'd have
the stone here with me.
That wouldn't be wise, now would it?
We're headed to our destination.
If we're not there in
time to set the device,
the red stone will be destroyed
and you will have nothing.
Look woman don't try to
fool me are you confident
that you and your minions
will be able to find
it in time the ball my
set is a very small one
but enough to damage the
stone and prevent its use
could this really be true she
never said anything whatever
i'll follow her lead were
Are you fellows listening?
If we don't stop it,
the bomb will go boom.
Even if true, we cannot
let you leave here alive.
Therefore, I have a suggestion.
Jojo and Mwabu can have
their fight one-on-one.
And Kaz, you and I will
also fight one-on-one.
And those who are left standing
will possess the stone. What?
The winners of this fight will have
the red stone and all of its power.
It'll be made very clear.
Which one of us will prove strong
enough to wield the stone's power?
Who is fit to survive?
The Pillowmen or humankind?
How dare you say?
Wamu.
Lord Kars, this is most absurd.
She is good.
She's just proven herself to be a better
gambler than I could ever dream of being.
No doubt.
You do have pluck.
Very well.
Then we will battle for the
stone, but don't get cocky.
You have no tomorrow
Using only words she just turned a dire
situation into more or less even odds.
Then so be it.
Let's do this
And so now we need to arrange a
time and place for our battle.
Wamuu, what are your thoughts?
We fight tonight under
the gaze of the full moon.
The arena at the base of Piz Bernina,
15 kilometers to the southeast.
We will meet at the Skeleton's
Heel Stone Circle there.
Many warriors have found death, glory, or
both throughout the history of that place.
In a stone circle?
Hey!
You can't just choose a place
because it happens to suit you!
Yes, Wamu.
I believe that to be a fine choice.
Now let's speak of the Red Stone.
Jojo!
You will bring the Redstone of Asia to
the Skeleton's Heel at midnight tonight.
And don't forget to remove the bomb.
The woman will remain
here with us as insurance.
Well, Lisa, Lisa?
They want to make sure that we
don't run away from the fight.
It is a reasonable request.
Jojo, go and fetch us the Red Stone.
You mustn't worry about me.
Would I?
I'll see you back at the arena.
Trust me, all right?
I assure you I do.
Caesar.
Until yesterday, I lived my
life thinking only about myself.
But now there's a new intense
feeling burning up inside of me.
Is this compassion?
I swear, I just want to destroy
those bastards and all their line.
I have to do it.
For Caesar and for Machina too.
Lisa, Lisa, and for everyone else I know.
I'll fight for you all.
Obviously, there's no bomb here
or anywhere else for that matter.
Lisa Lisa, even when you're under pressure,
you are one deceptive young woman.
Hmm.
Well now, maybe I should bring you a
change of panties in case you get scared.
Wait a minute.
What are these photos?
What?
It's Granny Arena.
What would Lisa Lisa be
doing with this? Huh?
Huh?
Who are these people?
May Knight, 1889?
50 years ago?
Then that young guy there is Speedwagon!
And Granny Arena!
And that straightzo, holding a baby!
Lisa, Lisa,
I don't know anything about your past or
the life you have led or who you've known.
What could you possibly be
doing with these photos?
I don't know.
it's genuine we accept your proposal
we honor you by fighting one-on-one
I suppose this means you saw the photos,
and you'd like to talk about it, right?
Actually, I had intended to
discuss this with you anyway.
Start with who you are.
Fifty years ago now, Iran lost her
husband on a ship sailing the Atlantic.
He was Jonathan Joestar, your grandfather.
That horrible day, your grandmother
saved the life of a baby girl.
That was me.
I am the baby in that photograph.
Wait a moment here.
That was 50 years ago.
So if you were a baby 50 years ago...
Hold on now!
Just how old are you anyway?
You're 50?
Oh, man, if you're 50, that
means then you're really old.
Is that right?
Normally, you look like
you're in your late 20s.
They say that harmon energy is
life energy and keeps you young.
I guess that explains why you really don't
act like a young woman
would behave at all.
Ah, I think I see a little
wrinkle back there. Yep.
Hey, I'm just kidding, all right?
Vampires, prepare the arena!
Light the fires!
There is not enough
time for us to talk now.
But we really do need to find the time?
Because our roots are deeply connected.
Our roots?
The stone mask killed my parents.
Iran was pregnant when she rescued
the little girl on the ship.
She couldn't raise two children,
so Straitzo became a father to me.
Straitzo as a father?
Are you serious?
Everything I know about
Harmon, Straitzo taught me.
He even gave me the red stone of Asia.
He did that?
Wow, this is all just so
unbelievable and hard to accept.
It's tragic beyond words
that the fear of growing
old drove him to commit
such acts of madness.
Jojo, my feelings about you defeating
him are extremely complicated.
But I believe that it was destiny.
What is there to say?
Everything, all of it, is so complicated.
What a bizarre relationship.
Lisa, Lisa.
She carries with her a
past painted by sadness.
It's time.
The rest of it will have to wait.
What's that rumbling noise?
They have come.
It was worth the wait.
The battle can begin now. No!
Huh? What's that? No!
Out of the way!
I don't care how many of
you get crushed! What?
What is that thing? A dinosaur?
No, I think a horse! That's a horse!
Lord Kars! Lord Wamu!
Please, move!
They've got Berserk!
I can't control them!
Lord WAMU, PLEASE!
Ah, these are fine steeds.
The stone masks worked extremely well.
They're now strong vampires. What?
Vampire horses?
On that track,
Jojo and Wamuu will face each other one-on
-one in a fierce
ancient-style chariot duel.
What do you mean?
An ancient Roman-style deathmatch.
You will battle, racing around the
arena trying to kill each other.
Lord Wamuu or Jojo,
who will be the first
one to fall under the
wheels or get beaten down by his opponent?
The loser dies!
Dies those are the rules.
Jojo the beasts have a hundred times
normal strength even lord Wamuu.
Can barely control them.
Hold it just a minute.
I will fight you on any
field or in any cage.
But vampires are your minions even horses.
So how is that fair?
Don't fret human the reins you use.
Will conduct hamon.
Wamuu will use his superior strength
and you can use your hamon to control.
Are you sure about that?
They look pretty vicious.
Be careful, they're mean!
That's true, but a
little hormone does help.
Wamuu, Wamuu, Wamuu, Wamuu,
Wamuu, Wamuu, Wamuu, Wamuu, Wamuu!
See, Wamu?
He has chosen an ancient
form for this battle.
That's a sign he means to win.
It's not for fun.
He's not going into this
for the sport of it.
He wants to take your life.
Just beat him, Jojo.
We have no choice but to win this.
There are no draws.
Wamu! Hey!
Did you notice that I haven't
taken this antidote yet?
I made a promise to Caesar that I wouldn't
drink this until after I took you down.
That promise is going to provide me with
a power I've never experienced before.
We'll face this fight together, Caesar.
Let's ride into battle!
I'll be the round and out, the
birds will make you one and out.
I'll be the round and out,
the birds will make you one and out.
Begin now!
You